
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Alrighty. 

Speaker 2  (00:03)
So let's start off with the application onboarding. Section, so tomorrow we discussed earlier today. We're I'm still waiting on that one application. 

Speaker 2  (00:15)
Although we're expecting a response pretty soon because they've gone through the legal hurdles, yep, correct? There's, we should be able to My response is Okay, alright, let's jump to the Application, all morning process. Okay, so we didn't we weren't able to get through this last week. 

Speaker 2  (00:56)
But let's see if we can get some updates here. So Paul, I know you did the poc. The quick poc on the technical parameters around token black times And then you wrote up a Wiki year confluence. 

Speaker 2  (01:15)
Under findings, right? 

Speaker 3  (01:18)
Yeah, yeah, it's just Anyway, we were just fogging that, you know, we can don't perform with standard, which is to define. Let's make a decision on what we're doing, and then publicize it. Finally enough, I get an in depth conversation on token lifetimes and standards that hits my inbox yesterday, right after I write that so fun times But my position until we decide otherwise, is that we don't provide the option. 

Speaker 3  (01:57)
To customize. Oh, we have to That's all that's it's just kind of a decision. 

Speaker 2  (02:17)
Let's try and see. I think editing provided a link To your assessment. 

Speaker 3  (02:26)
Yeah, it's it's a nut Jira, if you're trying to think, but if you click on that its nci story, it should be in the The notes. Yeah, there you go. Is it perfect? 

Speaker 2  (02:56)
Okay, anything else you want to share with the team here on your best assessment? 

Speaker 3  (03:03)
No, I think I already shared it with folks on an earlier call, so nothing different. It's been a good story for the track of the decision okay. 

Speaker 2  (03:17)
And then the other action item here was to cleanup that epic for the module improvement set. 

Speaker 3  (03:24)
I think it was split into lob Vs delivery modules, but it still needs up on my part. But it was tigmented between the LO bacing work and the delivery facing work. Exit a little cleaner looking, but still has some. 

Speaker 3  (03:49)
I haven't cleaned up the stories, cleanup or rejiggered the stories that are there. But the stories that are there, I think are pretty close to complete. There's just a couple of are completely defined, have the work completely defined in them, and I just need to close a couple that are in applicable and make sure the descriptions on others are clear. 

Speaker 3  (04:11)
And then there's summer finement from me needed for the bug fixes for some of the bug fixes that were identified. Yeah 

Speaker 2  (04:20)
Okay, sounds good. Paul, do you know how the the development work is going with Michael laudati? 

Speaker 3  (04:33)
Well, that's what I was saying is, so the most uncertainty I have and I still really haven't followed out, but the LOB facing module work, which is, I think I think that's to some extent, Germany needs to be back for some of the work there to kind of help define it a little better. It was, it's certainly in progress. But I don't know where it is. 

Speaker 3  (04:57)
And then the like, I was saying, the delivery facing Work, that's pending is on me to define better. Because the we know what the bugs are, but I don't know the right risk for mediation path. 

Speaker 2  (05:25)
So we don't know if it's on track for 

Speaker 3  (05:27)
Q3. At this point I would say, well, it's sorry, and there's a bunch of like, documentation and other process related stuff that's not definitely not going to finish. A module related work. 

Speaker 3  (05:42)
I also don't think so, because I get some time to dig into the APIs and figure out the right calls that will fix the problems. Not a strictly terraformed development issue. 

Speaker 2  (06:07)
And do you know if Jeremy's still meeting with the team every day? 

Speaker 3  (06:12)
It was out last week. I believe so. Yes 

Speaker 2  (06:29)
Okay, we'll just have to check with Jeremy, maybe next week. Anything else on? Soft server Improve events. 

Speaker 3  (06:48)
No, I think the one thing that I have even less of a beat on is the whole, so D rolls for the for the For James team to get access to terraform and such and our repos, to use the new deployment process, which is like it is In a usable state right now for most ssl use cases. There's still bugs, but it's so that was where, but I don't know I am unclear on whether that sod thing is going to be resolved anytime soon, or if they should just be getting them access to the legacy. Let's forget if someone decided that already, but we haven't been proceeding with getting them access to using the current roles. 

Speaker 3  (07:35)
Maybe partly because those are spread, those give access across a few repos, I think, and they only need the one. I can get ideas the sod either GitHub best Terra for adp GT sod thing this month just year next year situation. I think it would help guide the tactical approach. 

Speaker 3  (08:01)
Okay. Well 

Speaker 1  (08:02)
Paul, 3, maybe I don't It's it's Korean is kind of leading somewhat of that team side. Should we have a meeting with them and see maybe they can align their team. I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (08:19)
Because I don't know who actually validated that the team doesn't align. I guess I didn't 

Speaker 3  (08:27)
Well, we have in the absence of the special Delivery focused role we haven't really talked what the like, what the So D she like, you said, what the So what we would want the so D to look like, given Ed pt restrictions, so it's not so much that hey I think some if it was using the existing adp GT roles, I still think that the team could be provisioned into those roles and work in them. It's really a question of do we do that, or do we? Or do we wait for a target state role, considering how long that has taken to formulate? 

Speaker 3  (09:10)
So if the answer is, we should proceed with the current setup, then we do have to work out who should be in what role out of Korea's team and I think we can figure it out. 

Speaker 1  (09:23)
Now, I guess. I don't think it has to something have to be brought up. Something has to be figured out, right? 

Speaker 1  (09:30)
So I've just there's 2 sides of every corner. 

Speaker 3  (09:33)
If we, I guess it's just that decision on do we do, we ignore this whole sod future sod model may be available at some point ever and go with the current state. And I'm even though the current state is It's very much lots of back-and-forth and approval, intensive. And really You know, the addiction. 

Speaker 3  (09:54)
Especially things like at deployment night, it can be quite coversome or need, like you've basically like, two people need to be available on deployment nights, instead of one type saying. Well, for the first for the manual, more manual process, and it's just one person, which I think is more, right? That's more follow anyway. 

Speaker 3  (10:14)
That kind of decision. So if we just kind of make a decision, one way or another there, if they ask it, but that's the thing I don't have any visibility on those sod to change. So I don't know if they're imminent. 

Speaker 2  (10:32)
Okay. Yeah, I think that's another thing we just need to follow with Jeremy on. Okay, next up is deployments, release management. 

Speaker 2  (10:47)
So when you provide it kind of the requirements and a couple of items into the ticket as well. You've added. For what's needed, so I don't, I Don 't know what the next step here is. 

Speaker 2  (11:00)
Do we need to interview it on our call on Monday or 

Speaker 3  (11:05)
Are we? 

Speaker 1  (11:07)
Well, we can review it. I guess where I'm struggling is, is. Like I said, that's built around for creek. 

Speaker 1  (11:15)
Grina is very Use cases right, which is the S So but then on Monday last Monday, we start to have that discussion around well that might not be just a single use case as simple as we thought right there might be API there might be service credentials type things in those requests, and I guess that's the piece, I'm not too sure on, and I think that's the next stage is to clarify that those use cases. Like use case one, it does involve both teams or one I think that's kind of because what I heard with that is the M365, is they would just drop it and then direct the user to go over and create a tier ticket, right? 

Speaker 1  (12:02)
So 

Speaker 4  (12:05)
Yeah, what's my that was my next step as well for service. Now because in the latest walkthrough that we did with Paul and Neha, it was to walk through use cases where application teams don't need to make calls to ms 365 or adjis, but there's a new token exchange pattern, which is implemented in the sit, and for that we need to make a call. We need to add the token exchange scope, so need to discuss further with pollina on how we should handle requests for this type. 

Speaker 5  (12:44)
That's gonna be coming in through the centralized intake. 

Speaker 4  (12:48)
Yes 

Speaker 6  (12:48)
Yeah 

Speaker 5  (12:52)
The one side is just gonna be of that is just gonna be S So right? That's the piece that's going to come in and try I. D. 

Speaker 5  (12:59)
Yes, the other side is going to be provisioned in pink fed. Yeah, right. So that piece, yeah, is there? 

Speaker 5  (13:08)
Go ahead, Paul? 

Speaker 3  (13:08)
The token exchange access itself is technically provisioned at ID, and it looks it is API access to some extent, right, so it is an oas flow to to get the token exchange the token token exchange token. 

Speaker 5  (13:25)
Is that not something that we could handle with for those very specific cases? 

Speaker 3  (13:33)
Sorry it is, I think, but I think it would just be. That's A I think it's, it adds some sub process right on the pink fed side if they need token exchange, so maybe it would be something we need to track on the intake form as needing separate steps, or is it just or do we treat it like you said as well, we need to know on the Android. Whoever's setting up the sso, and the Android side needs to know that that configuration needs to be added to the antid app, and then the requesting team needs to know that they have to go to pink fed and get a new client ID to do token exchange. 

Speaker 5  (14:07)
To me, that's part and parcel of a single intake. Right? You know, because from the gecko, the teams are not going to know that they need that Warm of functionality. 

Speaker 5  (14:20)
I can't like, I just don't see that happening. Krena, and I have talked about this, I don't see a team showing up on our doorstep saying, yeah, I need to do token exchange. I think those just like we talked about this morning that, you know, some team's going to show up and want one thing or another, and we are going to identify like the combined team is going to identify that they need a token exchange right? 

Speaker 5  (14:44)
So to me, this is more at the moment, is more process. Yeah 

Speaker 3  (14:53)
So I agree on that I think we probably from our side actually, one thing I was thinking about today is we need to update our pattern documentation a bit. I'm on On that so that we can sort of recovered from a security perspective, by the way we have, by the way, we we interface with like csp and stuff. So we should update that try, and we need to update that to try and get the sort of that token exchange flow sort of considered a standard S is no pattern, because it's the current oedcat explicitly says like you aren't, you know, you're not asking for authorization to other APIs as part of the pattern. 

Speaker 3  (15:38)
So that's a but that's a relatively easy thing on our We just need to, but especially once the documentation on the token exchange pattern is sort of published and formalized, I'm not just asked get that get our own patterns amended, it makes you laugh it and do roidc, kind of S or oidc sso pattern. 

Speaker 5  (16:00)
Yeah, that architectural level pattern. A documentation is still pending, but you don't have that finalized yet, okay? So getting back to the whole, this would be one of the use cases that Wayne is attempting to document and define right so that we know exactly who has to do what where and we know what level of access is required on both sides of the fence to handle each of these individual use cases right for deployment purposes. 

Speaker 3  (16:36)
Yeah, but we're not as explicitly, I would say, not having Wayne handled right now. The general non, not pure. So you know, oh often I'm saying 65, whatever cases that's not. 

Speaker 3  (16:50)
You know, we won't change anything about how we deal with those right now. 

Speaker 5  (16:54)
Okay, so that won't deal with them, but we need to understand like if one comes in, we have to be able to recognize which team is going to, you know, how the handoff is going to happen, all that type of stuff, and that's what Wayne was going to look at into. 

Speaker 3  (17:09)
Okay, okay, right? 

Speaker 1  (17:11)
And so what I did do is I reached out to neon, I said, what other things do you guys do well at bondboarding, and she came back with skim, consistently grant the M365 APIs, so those are other use cases. I think like I said, we'd need to sit down. And make sure we understand does the skim affect. 

Speaker 1  (17:31)
Your team at all. I don't know that right and is that where we're missing misaligned on, you know, what's needed as far as those processes endure. 

Speaker 6  (17:40)
No, we need to map those out and work close, because I think they're being articulated verbally, but there's nothing anyone can go back to reference that flow to see what everything is touching. So that is something we have to draw Jane, or at least we're gonna have to spell out the service. Now, team. 

Speaker 3  (18:01)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (18:02)
And it was 

Speaker 3  (18:04)
It's a good example of one that's more complicated. I mean, I would say 65 related ones that are also So I would say, we still, we already built something into the form and into the predocumentation that explicitly says, that's not, that's not what this you know what, not what the ID as a so onboarding form is for go to, you know, confluence the future, the other ServiceNow form for the delivery team intake, but stim is an interesting one, because it's usually done sort of alongside an sso integration and needs to be correlated. 

Speaker 3  (18:38)
With it, but is not a necessarily integration So I at that one's a gap that we haven't really talked about how to deal with, because it's going to be, you know, the way it would currently work. They'd go sso through one channel and skim through another, and then you'd have everybody working, everyone would have to work together on what amounts to the same, deliver the same deliverable from an application side. 

Speaker 1  (19:02)
And that was by goal for kind of Mondays put on paper, what I kind of know, and what I think is there and have that discussion and say, what are we missing and what do we need to make sure they're on? That's why I think we're short. We're a little shortcoming on that, okay. 

Speaker 3  (19:21)
And then some of the, you know, the standards, I think we got clarified already for me, Wayne, which is like ym does not think the credential expert is required. I think we need to I am a really spun off any tasks to start getting standard changes in other stuff aligned. But I think that was more of a careena conversation around like, how is this going to work? 

Speaker 3  (19:44)
I think, the, you know, the ways of working conversations can be more of an operational conversation on like, you know, all of these tools that the pink fed team uses to get the job done that. Aren't available if you're doing something in antra, ID, are we going to try and replicate them or not? 

Speaker 1  (20:01)
Yeah And that's where I think you did that work on that table is If greena's team's doing this this way and getting these numbers and shoulda team kind of be doing the same thing that we could open that discussion up to I don't know, right, okay. Yes, I think that 

Speaker 3  (20:22)
It seems like it should be discussed. Okay, otherwise I don't know what's going to happen, right Like there's the teams do it different ways. So then the thing that team just starts implementing at trid, they need to say they're either going to do it one way or the other, they're not going to They can't use And if they're going to do it one way or the other, either the process or things around the process need to change 

Speaker 1  (20:49)
So two things, one is look at the use cases comparison, how they could affect them between the 2 teams. The other one is to see if teams should be aligning the overall. I'll say audit requirements for lack of a better term. 

Speaker 2  (21:16)
Hey, when there was another action around How we handle secrets? 

Speaker 1  (21:24)
Yeah, that's when Paul just mentioned. 

Speaker 3  (21:27)
Yeah, I think Wayne clarified that we don't need to have them expire ever basically. So we can update our processes right now on thed side, and then that's a that removes A I mean, really an operational process that we and every app team that integrates after ID, has to go through. 

Speaker 1  (21:47)
Let's put this way, you're not required to change them, but if there is a potential instance to compromise where they think that credentials been. Compromise, then you need to change it, right? 

Speaker 3  (22:01)
Yeah, how do you, I guess I should have asked, how do you know when that happened? 

Speaker 1  (22:05)
Well, it basically comes from the setups teams, right? So if they're right, if their logs show that somebody potentially is Hitting against the authentication module with, you know, that's credential, then If it's in doubt, you're going to change password, right? Yeah 

Speaker 3  (22:24)
So anyway, I'd like someone posted on it GitHub, or whatever. 

Speaker 1  (22:27)
Yeah It's found out out in the black quab, something like that. 

Speaker 3  (22:32)
Yeah, yeah, actually, the nice thing with NIT is there's some detective controls like that that are built into the platform, whether anyone is actually watching is a better question. But we don't let them be. We don't let the lobs handle them, so they have it, I think a very low. 

Speaker 3  (22:48)
Chance of being exposed. But if we're going to let lops handle them, then there's much more opportunity for it to, you know, be put in someone's GitHub, repo and post it out on the web, or something. So I think that's where if you can clarify, I guess. 

Speaker 3  (23:02)
If you can just clarify right the expiry practices and requirements then actually we might have some work around the making sure that the detective controls the entryd has around service. Principal secrets are actually the same kind of alerts that you get, because I suspect 

Speaker 2  (23:23)
Document that you posted. 

Speaker 1  (23:24)
No, no, see. It was requirements. Some relative to this I don't see what it has to say. 

Speaker 1  (23:35)
I think the onus round That is more or less the app. That's in those secrets right now, right now. But we do it, and then give them to the app, but the app would be the one It causes them to be exposed. 

Speaker 1  (23:50)
Yeah, I don't know, is that not something that becomes aware that ISIS that like in a sense that snow somewhere and is that being feed fed? Sock. Any information around like that? 

Speaker 3  (24:02)
When do I work? I was asking, what wait, how you guys even get alerted to who gets alerted to you're talking about compromise, you change it in the event of compromise, who's responsible for knowing that it's compromised and doing the change and who's notifies, that if they're It's like, how does that ever get to you? So we can make sure I know we have one detective control around service, principal secrets, which we, I don't think we've ever asked Cesar to set up like alerts for but they could easily do so because the date is already on the SIM. 

Speaker 3  (24:37)
But if you have a you know, but who does that go to I would assume it kind of goes to us? As worth the idp, but I just want to make sure we're doing the same thing that does for that, if we're going to start exposing the secrets. The potential lowb. 

Speaker 1  (25:00)
I have to take that one away and ask I don't know. Like I said, I was using that as an explanation of what that means, right? If it is even better 

Speaker 3  (25:15)
And I hadn't thought about belonging monitoring river Requirements, so that's just an artifact of finding out that we don't have to be so crazy about them, basically. As we are right now, and we can go to a less labor-intensive model. 

Speaker 1  (25:30)
Because I know soccer is searching dark web for credentials and secrets and other things like that. 

Speaker 3  (25:37)
Yeah, and that's where, like do they even know? It's like, fine, are they even looking for their compliant ids for Azure apps, or are they just looking for pink bed? I'm sorry I grew up an interesting I would be curious about that as much as sock ever tells anyone what they're doing. 

Speaker 1  (25:55)
That's what makes them sock. Okay, I will. I will take it away and see If there is any detection, I guess I'd tell No affairs, and I don't think there is, but It's, it's dependent on what the sock comes back with. 

Speaker 1  (26:13)
Normally it's what we see around 10, yeah 

Speaker 3  (26:17)
And I can, I mean, we talk with the stock about other stuff? So like, if we just need to make sure I mean, again, it's like As they have their own dark web scanning, but they don't know the right client ids and secrets to see if someone's linked it, then they might need to ingest certain kinds of data into whatever those custom processes are from Android. But if it's just a matter of they are already looking. 

Speaker 3  (26:40)
For that, and all we need to do is make sure the Microsoft alerts about hey, by the way, we saw this, you know, maliciously, because, you know, we saw this secret used from a malicious IP address, or something which are hitting in the platform right now, but I don't think are triggering anything we could easily. Ask for that to get added, and I think because it's a super low volume, they won't complain and say they need five people to deal with it. 

Speaker 2  (27:13)
All Mike and team, I think, one thing that's kind of slipped our radar for the last quarter was what Mike just left one thing that slipped our radar. I think, is the like, how do we handle N pits discussion? 

Speaker 3  (27:28)
So 

Speaker 2  (27:30)
I know, like we had a story for it, but I think that might need to be like a separate epic. I 

Speaker 3  (27:39)
It's like I don't even 

Speaker 6  (27:41)
Try to save the epic Mania till later for you. So you could get through your calls today, Andrew, that's why that's almost gonna be like a whole journey, but I had Murad, do some of the Foundational prep work, so we can have the discussion and make the updates pretty quickly. 

Speaker 3  (27:58)
But that's, that's like a right. What is the way that isn't kind of like an enterprise decision right on how we're dealing with inbits? So I would say, I would think that. 

Speaker 3  (28:08)
So that comes down from like a standards, architecture My perspective, and then we figure out how to implement it on the IDP level, it's not something we're like, I have absolutely no idea how I can tell you a few options for how I imagine npits are going to be handled. Gramma, fade, but I like like And there's some situations where I think Jeremy, or maybe you Jane have said, like, hey, yes, during app onboarding, perhaps coming in trid, we're gonna make them get rid of the N peds or like, get rid of shared N peds and blah blah blah, I like II don't think like we can solution from our end yet because I don't know what the requirements are. 

Speaker 5  (28:46)
That there have been there have been initial conversations along those lines, but you are right, we have to get back to those conversations and be able to handle those particular use cases. 

Speaker 3  (28:58)
No, anyway, it was just wary of like, yeah, it does, I do kind of think it needs to I don't know if it needs an epic because I don't know How much work it needs to have associated with it, but some sort of epic track that like there need to be decisions and sort of Standards create a refined on it so that we can then figure out what work needs to be done would be good. It would make sense is just, I don't think I can create an engineering hypothesis right now. Because I don't know what's needed right? 

Speaker 5  (29:33)
Yep, so we got a circle back to that. 

Speaker 2  (29:37)
Yeah, so I will start tracking this here, and then we'll have to figure out, maybe on the later call today, we can discuss Tracking, but Okay, we'll just leave this here for now. ServiceNow intake. So I mean, we kind of touched on that Do we need to make any updates based on the token exchange topic or 

Speaker 4  (30:05)
So it can remain the same 

Speaker 2  (30:09)
I can't, okay, sounds good. Our token exchange. I think some pretty good updates here from last week. 

Speaker 2  (30:22)
So BVOD kickoff is happening on Monday, so YM is having a chat with them just to kind of understand. Requirements, et, cetera, but do you have anything else to add there? 

Speaker 1  (30:37)
Yeah, that's more of a discussion with the line of business to ensure that they're aligned with t 

Speaker 3  (30:44)
The mfa requirements for it. 

Speaker 2  (31:01)
And then the ih app We got some timelines as well from that team, so they're targeting to Complete set move into Pat mid-august and then move to production in September. So I think that is overall good news. 

Speaker 3  (31:43)
I don't know, pal, I'll just put token exchange really quick. This is a this kind of speculative at this point, but I'll I just linked the ticket and chat for that's a possible another consumer for token exchange that I mentioned earlier. Another kind of another absent test with anyway, that's a midnight's minimal inflammation, but in the ticket Well, I'll i'll give information as they as they get more and then we'll do it. 

Speaker 3  (32:19)
You can take potentially with adding that functionality on 

Speaker 2  (32:31)
Export. Anything else we've opened exchange. All right, custom claims. 

Speaker 2  (32:45)
Does anybody have any updates on this one? We have to wait for Germany back. 

Speaker 3  (32:51)
I don't have any updates on the development work has talked to me a little bit about starting the idp side work to enable it. So I just need to He's spun up a few stories in my epic. That's still in refining to start doing the idp side configuration to handshake, but the app development part It's still in process, but I don't have updates on this specific epic. 

Speaker 3  (33:21)
Just the one that it'll start meeting some work on the idp side, but it's pretty light. Compared to the app development work 

Speaker 2  (33:45)
So epic is being refined, Paul. Yeah 

Speaker 3  (33:54)
Yeah, for the specific oh yeah, Android integration F yeah 

Speaker 2  (34:08)
Okay, sounds good. Thanks for the update there. Mfa, on vdi. 

Speaker 2  (34:20)
Spanish along Yeah, I just want to provide updates to the To the group here, I know, you provide them in our standup, but I think the group might be interested in the Partners that you've made. 

Speaker 3  (34:33)
Yes, so sure. So the 

Speaker 7  (34:36)
Short update is that the taste case validation is in progress. 

Speaker 1  (34:45)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (34:47)
It basically got most of the access that you need worked with Mike Fleming. 

Speaker 7  (34:52)
Yeah, that was done. Yeah. The week prior and also got the devil. 

Speaker 7  (34:58)
Laptop configured in a window software business, and all that and get the group membership and all that completed for various test accounts, and now in midstup, basically testing all the test cases. And all this work is being done in Dev, just an fi, I yeah. 

Speaker 2  (35:28)
Okay, so initial. So You completed the initial first 4 use cases a test cases. 

Speaker 7  (35:40)
So no, there's been more now, so I'm up to Usk S10. So 1 to 4 is done, then 5 to 7 cannot be completed within the dab and pad environment. 

Speaker 2  (36:00)
1 through 4 and I was at 7 through T. 

Speaker 7  (36:05)
2527, cannot be done. And Daring, bad, because the environment restriction is not available And then 8 to 10 is in progress. It's almost done So I can put it as done for now. 

Speaker 7  (36:20)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (36:25)
After 7. You cast the jet in death. 

Speaker 7  (36:41)
Actually, same thing will apply to 14 to 16 as well. If that cannot be tested within the Davin pad environment as well. 

Speaker 2  (37:01)
Discussion, I won't hear any discussion around higher environment testing. 

Speaker 3  (37:16)
Who wants to go on a trip to India to one of their clean rooms double hot? 

Speaker 1  (37:33)
Maybe there's something a little closer. I think I found the contact for eccentra. So their clean room 

Speaker 3  (37:42)
I don't 

Speaker 1  (37:44)
They're, they're actually looking to get their CSP approved. 

Speaker 6  (37:48)
My one hand so 

Speaker 1  (37:53)
I have a meeting hopefully next week with somebody 

Speaker 3  (37:58)
When was it like cleaning room in Hawaii or something? 

Speaker 1  (38:01)
I don't know where it is. 

Speaker 2  (38:06)
Man, as she separated out the Best cases from the use cases, right? 

Speaker 7  (38:13)
It does journey actually? But yeah, that was done. 

Speaker 2  (38:36)
Okay. And then Wayne, you're still looking into secure room. Use your identification and book of record. 

Speaker 2  (38:51)
How do you update star win? 

Speaker 1  (38:57)
Yeah, so I cut a noteback from the general mailbox, and they've given me a contact to reach out to for that. Like I said, I've the other one is center center. I found an honor for the one clean room anyway, so I got up trying to book a meeting with him next week to see what's there and how they onboard their people to find out who that how we can get a list of those people. 

Speaker 1  (39:35)
But as far as finding an individual listing of clean room people, I don't think that's I cannot see that happening. 

Speaker 2  (39:46)
Yeah, it's gonna be an issue. 

Speaker 1  (39:49)
I did not if we can get a couple of the big players. Maybe that might be the place to start right? 

Speaker 2  (39:55)
The Jeremy uniforming that email of Kashmir Bruno 

Speaker 1  (40:10)
I'm gonna say no I don't recall reading it, but From who it was for Jeremy. 

Speaker 2  (40:17)
Yeah, the era contacts somewhere. That you were 

Speaker 3  (40:24)
That was cash out right? I think he provided stuff. Yeah, just have. 

Speaker 2  (40:37)
It's a cushab with AV. 

Speaker 3  (40:39)
Yeah, oh, let me see if I get funded, and I have I was on that just many months ago. If he didn't It's because I have but Bate, J AI think It worked with him periodically, but this specific clean room topic came up liking to say like, sir and IA month ago or something. I'm Tyler forward that on yeah. 

Speaker 3  (41:08)
Yeah. Yeah, I actually, I just found it, so let me stand it playing. 

Speaker 1  (41:30)
Thought he did send somebody, but I thought he said, okay? So with discussion around getting use cases 

Speaker 2  (41:48)
Check, pay the Oscar. M fa on V. D. 

Speaker 2  (41:51)
I. 

Speaker 7  (41:53)
No matter this morning. 

Speaker 2  (42:04)
502 so 

Speaker 3  (42:09)
We 

Speaker 2  (42:10)
Okay, so provided 2. We Have a kickoff meeting later this afternoon to chat with the line of business. Here's business stakeholders on the Canadian retail side, so that's shortly after this call. 

Speaker 2  (42:30)
I guess maybe let's go through other updates here. Anthony's here as well. Anthony, do you want to provide any updates on the use case work that you're working with Jeremy on? 

Speaker 8  (42:46)
No, not right now, as you know, Jeremy's on vacation. He shared the link and also a Word document through the previous meeting. So right now, nothing more to share, okay. 

Speaker 2  (43:11)
Initial draft. I've been shared with t In the retail audience Let's kick off. Okay, Katie. 

Speaker 2  (43:50)
Yeah, so I guess the context here is that Anthony yourself and Jeremy were asking for validation of use cases as well as a review. And also, some questions are provided to The retail audience, the current standing touch points that we have Didn't have the correct correct stakeholders to answer those business questions, such as like, what happens on day? One for a retail user. 

Speaker 2  (44:23)
Where do they start start? There are things provision to them. And so that's why we needed to do the kickoff, first, with the business side so that we can engage them to help us answer some of those questions. 

Speaker 2  (44:40)
And so that's why we're doing the kickoff today. 

Speaker 8  (44:44)
Yeah, I guess we have to start somewhere because we got to identify the owners I through some exercise. And hopefully this solves the problem. 

Speaker 6  (45:00)
Yeah, yeah, we need to have that conversation with the direct owners, you can catch her, those use cases, and there's, well, you're getting the most from an architect viewpoint. I gotta hearsay 

Speaker 1  (45:18)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (45:21)
I guess the contact that I've been working with deemi. She's been kind of rallying the troops on the business side. She's kind of mentioned a couple of times questions around day 2, who's supporting whatnot think I'm gonna start try to steer away that conversation for later. 

Speaker 2  (45:36)
Today, because I think that's a little bit far out. 

Speaker 6  (45:39)
Yeah, I've just started there for your reference. I just sent an email to Jane. I just did the intro of you because and Mom, and we're getting those coffee, we're still on, like the estimation phase, we're not ready yet to start having, like, you know, everyone on a call yet, and talk, and we got a little, we'll talk later, we got a ways to go, but the wheels are in motion. 

Speaker 6  (46:01)
But they're ahead of the game. 

Speaker 2  (46:06)
Okay? Um. Not sure if there's any updates on idv other than Jane, you and I were discussing that there might be a kind of an idv light possibility. 

Speaker 5  (46:21)
Yeah, we're we're, we're looking at exactly that possibilities of trying to support phyto ii. The ub K provisioning first was But that's a voter that has only it's just been like a plan, this guy idea at the moment. 

Speaker 6  (46:43)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (46:54)
I have aged. Lexus Nexus to discuss Okay? And then Last week we discussed some testing was completed, such as pre-registration. 

Speaker 2  (47:20)
Cruise mention of additional test cases to be conducted. And Jamie was going to provide some of those items to Ben. Anybody knows those were provided to Ben and if there are any mother, Peter? 

Speaker 2  (47:38)
The best case is completed. 

Speaker 3  (47:41)
I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (48:11)
Okay, sounds good. Here we go manage services. Engagement, I think there's been good progress from what I've heard. 

Speaker 6  (48:22)
I think. And I've seen the wheels starting to move with people reaching out. It seems that it's not officially assigned in area yet, but it's gonna be approved. 

Speaker 6  (48:33)
And it's just gone through its final coding of pain. I guess Jane. 

Speaker 5  (48:41)
Why not coding of what paint? Oh yeah, yeah, it's There's a little bit of hot potatoing with this, but yeah, we'll get it finished. 

Speaker 6  (48:57)
We're no longer worried that it's not going to get approved. 

Speaker 2  (49:01)
Okay. Anything specific that we wanna mention here on the record for this 

Speaker 6  (49:13)
That's all I know right now to him say anything to you is Jane. You had that question earlier I gave him that we filled that out a couple times though, I wish they would keep the forms at the recent them. 

Speaker 5  (49:26)
I think there was some confusion over whether or not there was a natural new eye and there were extended questions about the UI. 

Speaker 6  (49:33)
And now you're doing that form, there is no UI and A 

Speaker 5  (49:37)
So no TD employees resources are going to be logging into anything within ubico. 

Speaker 3  (49:47)
I okay, I was gonna say I I wasn't sure if there was any sort of management portal of some kind of like was the configuration that we'd lug into. So 

Speaker 6  (49:57)
There might be, but that would be like maybe like me, you and Jane Paul and like a breaklass scenario and someone with somewhere weird, and we need to place an ad hoc order to ship a key. 

Speaker 3  (50:10)
Okay, and now yeah, we would be lucky and regularly, so okay. 

Speaker 5  (50:14)
So there is AUI 

Speaker 6  (50:17)
There is we get it and we get access as soon as the msa is complete, they get us set up, they give it us our tenant right? And you know, obviously we wanted. We could not do it integration, and we could all just take orders in our emails and punch in addresses machine. 

Speaker 5  (50:34)
Yeah, yeah, I get it. Yeah, it just this is one of these things that gets app in vm and ssg land so okay, we may have to go back to a pander, and let her know that there is E UI for this. But other than that, yes, things are progressing well. 

Speaker 6  (50:53)
But when they asked on their form, they were talking about the devices 

Speaker 5  (50:57)
I know, because they were using, we have to interpret those things for them, and we have to point stuff out because they don't They don't recognize that stuff those nuances and those responses right? So that's, you know, that's why we get into these fins, or we gotta go. 

Speaker 6  (51:13)
So we got Braille ub keys. 

Speaker 5  (51:16)
They need those yeah, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (51:22)
Okay, and the mic were able to initiate the spid for this 

Speaker 6  (51:27)
I didn't even have to. It was such luxury Andrew. Because this is becoming cadinile, getting to that deeper. 

Speaker 6  (51:35)
Me and Jane just have to really provide the resources, and we have funding. And apparently these track leaders, Jane are doing all that for us. 

Speaker 5  (51:44)
Except I believe the spid was submitted, but it was submitted into the wrong org, so I think the spid may have to be redone if it hasn't been redone already so spid work is underway. Andrew, we just have to get the direction of the spid work correct? 

Speaker 2  (52:12)
Gosh sounds good. I also did see some emails back-and-forth between Jonathan and the H. I. 

Speaker 2  (52:23)
D. 

Speaker 5  (52:24)
Yes, yes. We will have to, and I've been talking to Mike about this as well. We are going to have to start process to engage the H. 

Speaker 5  (52:38)
I. D. That group. 

Speaker 5  (52:42)
Or through the SSGVM process as well to get the NFC readers. 

Speaker 6  (52:48)
So Jane with that I'm confused because we've already done estimates for that. Why would we go sign a direct managed service? 

Speaker 5  (53:00)
I'm just, I am not saying that we're going to go directly to the vendor I'm saying we're going to engage ssg, and 

Speaker 6  (53:08)
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (53:09)
They can do whatever they do behind closed doors. 

Speaker 6  (53:13)
Come, we went to them for an estimate on as Jane. I was pulling 10 different directions and have a 1 cooked email to you with it on it that I just haven't hit send yet because I got 5 others like it on various other subjects. But citi, David ssg was just gonna engage cdw, because this came up when we were doing the ubico, managed service contract, and if we wanted to do it as a part of that, and we didn't, because we were going to come back to Fiona from cdw, who I was going to see you on the email and get an updated estimate, or have her. 

Speaker 6  (53:51)
Send me the old one if she could find it, I don't know if it's in my archives, or it's been a while, but we were we had a deal where SSG end up, well, you know, you know who it was, he Vander, who's gone I guess, not over there anymore. Andrew was the guy that got us the original cell for the ub keys and was working with CD W and was gonna Come back, we were ready and we were just gonna do a quick sal at cdw. Jane to provide the readers because we can get it cheaper and quicker than And less painfully than an msa. 

Speaker 5  (54:27)
Okay, and that's yeah, we just have to follow a process I'm just I just want to get it started. There has been some more consideration as to the form of NFC reader, and I have to talk to Jordan about this, given that those NFC readers are going to have to handle both phyto ii as well as OTP, pretty much at the same time, right? So we have to make sure that NFC readers have the right functionality for our use cases. 

Speaker 6  (54:54)
I was presenting you about that link, I wanted to disassemen to make sure it was the double OTP final 2 on that Jonathan was posting around, and I couldn't find the link for it to make sure on her estimate was just the one you guys were looking at and not like a cheaper one. If so give us the updated estimate. You can go back to SSG because we'll need to do that chain, because our old SSG person that we were in touch with is No longer here or not. 

Speaker 6  (55:26)
Working in that group anymore, I don't know what the story is, but 

Speaker 5  (55:29)
Yeah, we'll go back to sayed then, because I had still working on the obviously the libico stuff. Mom, and we'll get we'll engage sied, and for this as well and see where he considers 

Speaker 6  (55:42)
Ask, tell him that the former contact was working with funera. Griffith, when cdw she's the td contact. 

Speaker 5  (55:51)
Okay, riffy. 

Speaker 6  (55:54)
She was working with Adam Some artists and obviously grander hoot remember Alabama hoot, the original side. 

Speaker 5  (56:07)
Okay. Biona, Griffith. 

Speaker 6  (56:13)
Yeah, I could send you the email if you weren't working for it, I guess she's a CD W contact for all of T. 

Speaker 5  (56:20)
He got anything or sent me the email 

Speaker 2  (56:31)
Sounds good, I think that's all for today. Mainstream, I think we have a pretty good handle on where that is. And then I got a drop for that kickoff, with Canyon retail. 

Speaker 6  (56:44)
Jane, I think she's on-site either in terrorists or 320, she comes in. 

Speaker 5  (56:50)
She's not in my dining room and Ajax. Like so that's as far as I'm going okay. 

Speaker 6  (56:56)
Yeah, well, there's an email, give her a give her this, reach out there. She's nice, tell her I sent her your way it's about Hoo D scanners we mentioned a while ago. When she was ordering, Sr bow keys were So now 

Speaker 5  (57:14)
Okay, awesome. 

Speaker 2  (57:16)
Thanks, everybody, thanks. Bye 
