
Speaker 1  (00:00)
And so I'm going to take the call for him, and then he, by the way. You're supposed to. What are you talking about? 

Speaker 2  (00:08)
Now really appreciate it. Thank you Another moment who the move for those I can't attend. Yeah, so it's a fairly. 

Speaker 2  (00:19)
Maybe I'll just kick it off. We are at 301 right now. So thank you, everybody for joining. 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
I know, this is a fairly big group. This is a kickoff from retail BBD perspective. About an enterprise wide initiative. 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
What the hope is here, as part of the agenda is just to introduce the initiative. Not necessarily going to introduce our bbd E Partners on the call, but introduce our technology Partners that are leading this initiative. Again, it's an enterprise mfa rollout, similar to windows hello for business. 

Speaker 2  (00:54)
And maybe what I'll do at this moment, and in time kick it off over 2 Andrew who's the PM supporting this For the enterprise sober, do you Andrew? 

Speaker 3  (01:07)
Hi, everybody very nice to meet you all excited to share kind of what's coming next after windows will for business and yeah, I'll just do quick intros, and we'll jump right into it. So myself, Andrea, yakoo, I'm the PM responsible for the overall enterprise mfa. Rollout program and so as you may have been familiar with when those rollout for business, that was kind of the previous phase of this, where we were, enabling a stronger authentication for laptop sign in for individual laptops, next phase of the program essentially covers all the remaining use cases, including shared desktops. 

Speaker 3  (01:48)
Mete's patrol desktops, as well as mainframe access as fall. So yeah, we 'll jump into those details, but we also have on the call, a lot of the A project stakeholders, including the owner of these capabilities, Jane petchka. I don't know if she's on the line just yet, maybe just jumping from previous call and then a few other project stakeholders, as well from global security and defense. 

Speaker 3  (02:20)
So yeah, pleasure meeting you all and feel free to stop me for any questions throughout the presentation and then we'll kind of discuss closer to the end, if people have any questions or concerns around responsibilities but yeah, I feel free to put your hand up or just stop me, and let me know if you have any questions. Okay, so let's get started here. So here's today's agenda. 

Speaker 3  (02:51)
And thanks again for joining on a Friday afternoon, trying to make this quick so introductions and overview of the a program. For roadmap timeline, we'll discuss roles and responsibilities from the bbde side next steps like what to expect, and we'll leave some time for questions. Okay, so what are we doing essentially, we are trying to improve multifactor authentication across the entire org, and what that looked like as I mentioned previously was starting with individual laptops that was a possibly finding and regulatory remediation project that was that had to be completed by June 30th of yeah, that was us month and moving forward. 

Speaker 3  (03:48)
We need to further secure, so we have additional milestones, and we need to secure all the remaining workstations, pdi, mainframe etc. And we need to essentially roll out a mfa factor for all colleagues across the bank. The reason we need this is because number one enhances security across the organization that also helps us meet our regulatory expectations, so we have additional regulatory requirements to abide by new authentication standards. 

Speaker 3  (04:22)
And basically each colleague needs to have a second factor for authentication by the end of Q2 of fi, 27. And so today, we have the ability to enroll into ms. Authenticator everybody who has an individual laptop, is enrolled into an assault for business, and so the next type of authenticator that we need to roll out is physical tokens for those that cannot use ms, authenticator and those that require to Use the share workstations. 

Speaker 3  (05:00)
So maybe I'll just pause there and see if there's any questions. The form factor here would essentially be a physical token that's seen here on the screen, so we're working with a vendor called ubco, to secure these hardware tokens that could be inserted into a workstation and tapped, as well for use with a card reader. So that I'll just see it, see a positive or see if there's any questions or immediate reactions from the group here. 

Speaker 1  (05:34)
So Andrew, sorry, every colleague needs to carry this Ubiquity, with them or 

Speaker 3  (05:42)
Yeah, it'll be anybody that has to Access and shared workstation, we're still working through those use cases to figure out exactly who that will be, but yeah, we're looking at the majority of the retail users will need to carry this physical key. 

Speaker 1  (06:06)
Yeah, and then I'm assuming, do we need to like trap? Sorry, I will have a 1000 questions. Do we need to then like track these keys and get them back like, I'm thinking like ceas, for example. 

Speaker 1  (06:23)
Like Cas are going to need these keys? If I leave the company, do I return it like. 

Speaker 4  (06:28)
Joey, that's exactly where my thoughts just went with the CEO program. I'm like, and a former bm also that like them having Microsoft authenticator and now they're like great Nancy don't even have the td apps, except for like minimal ones. So now they're going to have to have the authenticator app every CAA, I'm assuming. 

Speaker 3  (06:50)
Yeah, so maybe to help alleviate some of the concern, we are working with the vendor that That makes these keys to help with the managed service, so they will be responsible for majority of the provisioning and And still to be determined whether we're going to ship them out to the individual users or to the branches, and how we're going to go from there, but we're basically leveraging that vendor to help us with parts of the management of these 

Speaker 5  (07:26)
So Andrew Sherri, as one of those opts, is one of those options that these would be That someplace secure in the branch, and when the staff come in, they grab them to use them and put them back. 

Speaker 3  (07:45)
I think specific use cases are still ongoing. I don't know if somebody from the engineering team would like to chime in, but I think the idea is for each colleague to keep keep the key on hand. 

Speaker 5  (08:01)
Yeah, that's what I that's what I was worried about. Honestly. Yeah, that's why I was suggesting that, maybe, you know, there's an alternate solution to actually keeping them in branch, okay. 

Speaker 6  (08:12)
I think conceptually right, I think that we're still talking about some of that, but from a security perspective, this is going to be, I mean, that's basically like leaving your password out somewhere, right because this will be your way of sending into your computer and to mainframe improving it to you, so certainly leaving. It somewhere shared where anybody can pick it up and prove to try, you know, sign it as And somebody else is not a great option. This isn't the second factor in this case, it's actually the way that you log into certain systems on its own. 

Speaker 6  (08:46)
Good luck, you wipe you swipe it over the reader on your computer, you sign into the computer directly. You don't need that plus a password or something. You may need your password for some other stuff, but you don't need it anymore, so it certainly couldn't be kept in a shared area where just anyone could pick it up and mfa as somebody else. 

Speaker 6  (09:05)
There's still, I guess there's still a pin requirement so there is still some knowledge requirement, so I guess I bet I don't. Not that I don't know how that a shared storage space matches with that. 

Speaker 5  (09:17)
Okay, yeah, I'll let I'll let everybody else ask the other questions. Because I have so many red flags lying around in my head right now, I'm sure somebody else is gonna is gonna come up with some more questions. 

Speaker 3  (09:28)
And Chris said, do you want to go next? 

Speaker 7  (09:31)
Hi, so I know we've mentioned this, I mentioned this on a previous call that we had, but I wanted to see if there's been any more insight when we're talking about these logins in terms of the shared data. The desktops. Things like the cdu crus, how those machines are going to work as they have a generic blog empty. 

Speaker 3  (09:53)
Yeah, I know that they've been mentioned. I don't think that we currently have a solution for that, but yeah, certainly been mentioned a couple of times Yeah, I don't have an answer for that at this time. 

Speaker 7  (10:06)
All right, no, no, no worries. I just wanted to see if there was an update on that. Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (10:14)
Alexandra. 

Speaker 4  (10:16)
So my question is I understand that this is like their main point to log in, call it a key, just like a branch key, is there going to be something in manager's Handbook, like an attestation for these keys? And then second to that, like, have we thought about, and I'm just gonna call it out a CAA, forgetting their key at home, and the impact to the branch of them having to leave and go back like, is there any I'm just, I'm just thinking about the retail space and C eas, and how like new onboarded, Cas might not understand the seriousness of having this to bring this key in right, some of them, I mean, we have her calms on our body. 

Speaker 4  (10:55)
And what have you. So first question is, is there something a manager's Handbook? Mandus key is to be secured safe, they sign off on it. 

Speaker 4  (11:03)
Second question is the what ifs? 

Speaker 2  (11:07)
Maybe I'll jump in there Andrew, that hasn't been discussed yet. It's a great question, great recommendation in terms of the controls for it, but I do believe that that is something that we, the teams would look at. Maybe Trish might want to, I 

Speaker 8  (11:24)
I was just going to say the same thing I guess is the first time hearing like I've really been brought in here so I as far as I know, there's nothing in BHP right now, but we'll have to look at how to see what that will look like. Today, branch managers or any keyholders are documented as having keys in the bhb, and then they attest to it, so I think we're going to need to look at that and what that will look like. 

Speaker 4  (11:44)
Okay, thanks. That's that's all for me for now. 

Speaker 1  (11:49)
Andrew, sorry, Jody again, just to I think it's a quick question, just so I'm understanding. I could see the picture. But is there like, do they have to have the key Read or whatever like one or the other and Microsoft off the authenticator or is the option that they would have either or of those 

Speaker 3  (12:10)
Yeah, I think it's going to depend on your role I would imagine. So for example, a branch manager, they may be enrolled into a mass authenticator because they And you know, they use it to sign into 

Speaker 6  (12:30)
Well I would love to see whether the stuff yeah. 

Speaker 3  (12:34)
Other applications, but possibly, if they kind of jump on the floor and they need to sign into the workstations, and yeah, they may need a ubiquity as well, so I think it's really role dependent. 

Speaker 6  (12:46)
But usually I would say, I think the goal in most cases would be, you know, you'd be, you'd be using the same form factor for like the same. If you're on a desktop right, and your mfa to mainframe, and it's a shared desktop, you'd also be using that same ubic, to sign in. So there's certainly some cases that we, I think we're still able to work on defining where people might need both, but they'd be situations where they're using their phone for BYOD, but they're also signing into the floor desktop for mainframe for some reason. 

Speaker 1  (13:18)
Okay, cause my head is going to and there's probably better experts on the club than me. Is everyone in branch is going to need a key. Because if they jump on the front line, they need a key, if they use the shared, there's a word for them and zar would know like the like. 

Speaker 1  (13:35)
The shared laptops in the off off area where they would go do their training like all of those, so I think everybody is going to need a key if I understand 

Speaker 6  (13:45)
Correctly, pretty much any shirt, anybody who uses a shared Andrew concurrence, if I'm wrong, anybody who uses a shared machine is probably going to need a cubic key, there might be some situations where something else works. But that's That's dedicated machines. Well, dedicated laptops, as we know, are windowsillo for business, but shared machines generally, because windows hello for business doesn't work that well on them or doesn't work that smoothly, something like the ubiq will be, I think the main option 

Speaker 3  (14:19)
I'll pause because I see lots of other hands Krista. 

Speaker 7  (14:24)
I dare sorry to ask again, but Paul mentioned this earlier in terms of ease of using this as a login, instead of password in login, ID so from a workforce perspective, are we expecting this to take shorter time than entering their login and password, because ceas, pbas, anybody working on the front line on those shared desktops, every time that they walk away from that desk desktop, they have to lock that monitor so when they go get cash from the cru, they have to lock it when they go talk to their manager, they have to lock it, which means every time they come back, they have to log in. 

Speaker 7  (14:59)
So if this is a process that might potentially take a little bit longer, then they're login ID and password. Then we're going to have that into every transaction time as well. 

Speaker 6  (15:11)
I don't think we've done timing. My guess would be that it's faster. 

Speaker 7  (15:17)
It's a pin, okay? We would have to do some time. Yeah, we would have to do some timing on it. 

Speaker 7  (15:20)
And I don't know 

Speaker 6  (15:22)
Yeah, it hasn't been Android physics supposed to time frames, I'm like, get it into the branch lab at X time, but that would be probably the place We could do some 

Speaker 7  (15:32)
Okay, permit, it's only because 

Speaker 6  (15:34)
Yeah, it permanently needs to be tested. I understood that you need to understand that you need to understand the time process impact. 

Speaker 7  (15:45)
Yes, absolutely only because it's regular regulatory that they have to have their monitor locked at all times that they're not at it. So it This could potentially add some time, especially for like cashing cash outs, right? 

Speaker 6  (15:58)
Yeah, yeah, this is 

Speaker 3  (16:00)
Yeah, I think we've we've been in some sort of initial discussions with the with the labs to get some of these hardware pieces in there and do some tests, but I think timing can certainly be a part of the initial testing. Chris said, does it help answer your question? 

Speaker 7  (16:22)
Oh, sorry, yes, sorry I was, we've, I figured we were moving on. 

Speaker 3  (16:27)
Okay. 

Speaker 8  (16:31)
Sorry, I just want to ask one question. So this is when they're gonna swap the ski and then enter in their acf, too, and that's what will give them the access. Because I don't know if it's like, is it? 

Speaker 8  (16:43)
That's like, are we saying it's that simple for I will 

Speaker 6  (16:47)
I think I haven't seen. I'm trying to think if we have this documented somewhere. I believe you just scan the key, and then you enter a pin. 

Speaker 6  (16:55)
I think you're basically because it knows who you get. And so I believe you skip the acf 2 entry part, but I think, well, we can definitely provide more detailed documentation from testing. 

Speaker 8  (17:07)
And so that means that like our frontline colleagues would have to set up or get set up with a pin, so that's what's personal to them. 

Speaker 6  (17:15)
Yeah, the pen. The pen is paired with the physical key, so you have an individual that proves you are the person who sort of that's, that's the second factor right. One is something, you know, and then that's when the key is something you have, so you do the combination of the key. 

Speaker 6  (17:33)
And the pin that's specific to that key, as opposed to being a general password. 

Speaker 3  (17:41)
No worries, Michael. 

Speaker 9  (17:43)
I just have 2 questions number one, is there a plan to pilot this, or is this just something that's just gonna roll out across the network all at once. 

Speaker 3  (17:53)
Yeah, absolutely, and we'll get to that in the next slide. So okay 

Speaker 9  (17:57)
Maybe I can just go with my second question, then I'll hold off until a second slide, can you just I know this meeting started off we started talking about we know solo, and this is kind of an extension of that but and don't know if I am cleared on like, why are we doing this? Right now they use a user password to log in right. The difference here is now it's a key and pin. 

Speaker 9  (18:25)
So like, what's the like, what are we solving for here? Is it just further security? Because if I have somebody else's pin and I have their key, I'm logging in, just like if I had their user and their passcode? 

Speaker 3  (18:39)
Yeah, it's a higher level of assurance. And Paul, I don't know if you want to chime in there. 

Speaker 6  (18:43)
Yeah, I guess so you need. I guess the idea is largely, but you need two things, right? You need to have them tell you there They're penned, and you need to have physical possession of the key, so that's the something you have, and something, you know, instead of something that, you know, and then the other thing that's more secure about it is that the pin is specific to the key. 

Speaker 6  (19:04)
So like it's not something you're using to sign in to like various applications like your password. So it's a lot less. Risk of compromise. 

Speaker 6  (19:15)
So various regulators, it's much more secure, and it's starting to be sort of the, I would say the enterprise standard for how to secure a sensitive transactions, like access to like signing to your desktop and mainframe, and then I think down-the-line a lot of applications are going to be integrated. With mfa requirements so like right now, very few applications actually require you to do mfa to sign in that application, but I think the editor Jane can provide the regulatory requirements but the regulators are requiring that hundreds if not thousands of enterprise applications require mfa to sign into them. 

Speaker 6  (19:59)
And given that right Now TV doesn't At least the idp that we're moving to antriid, doesn't provide anything that you can just like. You can't achieve that the only way to achieve that is with your phone, and that's not an available method for I think for branch people on the tether line etc, so we need to provide this additional security option, and if you sign into your desktop with this security key, it counts as mfa, for any application, you're signing into, and with the notable exception and mainframe, I mean, you don't ever need to like kind of re-enter that information in order to securely access applications that have been secured with mfa requirements. 

Speaker 6  (20:42)
That might be good, little bit into the weeds, but 

Speaker 9  (20:45)
It's okay, so it sounds like this is like regulator like regular, heavily regulator regulator influence. If you 

Speaker 6  (20:52)
Yeah, yeah, but this is if we didn't have addition, right? I get I gu The bank wants to secure access better, I'm sure for our own reasons, but the regulators are also saying, you know, any of your applications that are doing sensitive operations need to have mfa applied to them and for someone who's on, for instance, a teller line who can't have their phone there. To do mfa, this is really what we believe to be the best option for meeting those requirements without causing people to have to, you know, enter a code every 20 minutes for this, or that application or bring their phone under the teller language, they're not allowed to do so this is kind of the that seems like the best available option, even if it does, certainly like there are recovery. 

Speaker 6  (21:39)
Use cases that are going to be more involved than like calling to get your password reset, or something that will go into when we get those fully defined. 

Speaker 9  (21:50)
Yeah, yeah, not long when we actually went out with, I think we supported an initiative around like construction around mobile phones and stuff in retail ranches, so this kind of conflicts with that, but I see that there are alternatives there, so no, thanks to the clarity. 

Speaker 6  (22:06)
No, the end and sorry, I think our understanding is that the mobile phones are not allowed in the branches. So that's that's the reason for the UV key. Okay, if mobile phones were allowed everywhere, we'd probably be in much warm in authenticator heavy guidance And what we understand that that's not, you know, not everyone's work situation can allow you to have a mobile phone there. 

Speaker 6  (22:26)
So-and-so the ubiquity is kind of the umb. The option for those scenarios 

Speaker 3  (22:35)
Okay, we have 7 minutes. I saw. Thank you very much for all the questions. 

Speaker 3  (22:40)
I'll just quickly skim through the remaining slides and then pause again for further questions. Okay, let's move on. So next slide here is just very high level timeline. 

Speaker 3  (22:55)
Currently, this quarter we've been working through high level use case development understanding who's impacted doing initial engagement, defining a change strategy, setting up success metrics, etc, next quarter, we're looking to kind of build this out, finalize the design work together with business stakeholders, to understand the specific use cases. And they in the life kinds of scenarios, so that's why we need your help and your engagement they've all been kind of communication plans and doing a soft launch on the mainframe side as well. 

Speaker 3  (23:35)
So we are pushing capabilities to for mainframe sign in by the end of October, although no unrelevant yet for on, a user basis Q1 kind of like a prelaunch, engaging in the change network doing Initial socialization, etc, and doing some final work on the design if required. And then kind of gearing up for Q2 for the actual rollouts, I don't have in this specific slide the branch pilots, but that's been discussed, and I think that'll happen probably closer to the beginning of the next calendar year. 

Speaker 3  (24:16)
So we need your help to kind of select a couple of branches to do those pilots, and then yeah, full rollout. Basically in the second quarter of next year and then yeah, after rollout, basically just monitoring optimization refining, kind of any additional support processes. Or cleanups are required, so that is the high level roadmap here. 

Speaker 3  (24:49)
Any questions on the slide. Move on to the next one. So this is just at a high level, what we understand what deemy's help kind of provided list of teams and potential stakeholders to work with. 

Speaker 3  (25:12)
I think dimi, you'll probably take this away with the team here to understand who should attend kind of some of our workshops who we need to engage. Throughout this project, and so I'll just probably just quickly skip over the slide, and I'll leave it up to you. And the team here to discuss further. 

Speaker 2  (25:33)
Perfect, thank you, maybe I'll just add like as a follow-up to this kickoff call is we'll set up a meeting just with the bbbe team just to look at the roles and responsibilities, and just the different working groups to support these changes to look for that in calendar. Next week. And if there is anybody else that does need to be included from the meeting minutes, please do forward and let me know. 

Speaker 3  (25:59)
Okay, and then this is the last slide to 4 questions, additional questions, what's next, and what do we expect for people? So our team is currently billing out and has built out an initial list of use cases I think it's about a 100 different use cases the help of Anthony here on the call. We've shared that with Devi, and some of the technology stakeholders, and next step would be to, uh, A Validate those use cases maybe have a couple of business requirements. 

Speaker 3  (26:30)
Workshops understand like I mentioned in the life of a Canadian retail worker. And it's kind of get your perspective. If there's any concerns issues, any recommendations would be very helpful. 

Speaker 3  (26:48)
And also to discuss the EU support, and are there some concerns around there, so those discussions are definitely required. After that, we'll take over all the inputs and feedback to build and complete the design. So that'll happen in Q4 Then, after we do that, well, we go to the retail, well, I think, in parallel, we'll be working with the retail lab with some initial testing, and then we'll kind of move on to the branch pilots. 

Speaker 3  (27:21)
From those pilots who were taken feedback, see how those go and then maybe go back into the drawing board if we need to and then from there go into the full robot, so this is pretty much at a high level, next steps where we would need some of your help and engagement to make the successful and yeah, very very happy to meet with you all and connect with you. Let you know what's coming and yeah, I guess I'll just open the floor again to questions for the last minute. 

Speaker 1  (28:00)
Ryan ER Andrew's Jody again, I know you just keep mentioning pilots, so I just wanna call out. There is a process for branch banking pilots that you would work really closely with. Ryan, my colleague, who's just on vacation today, so just before you go too far down the path, I just want to color that we have to be involved on our side, because there's a process and approvals and plans that go into place to that, so as Ryan works with you on the change piece. 

Speaker 1  (28:30)
He can talk to you about the pilot process, okay? 

Speaker 3  (28:34)
It makes really appreciate that. Okay. Any other thoughts before we close this off? 

Speaker 3  (28:49)
Okay, awesome. Thank you so much for your time. I'll be in touch with dimi, and I guess dimi, you'll be working with the stakeholders here and let us know who to engage for the next steps. 

Speaker 2  (29:02)
Thank you so much, Andrew and team and hope everybody has a great rest of the day and I'll send a copy of this deck and just next steps for the next meeting with the group. So thank you. 

Speaker 3  (29:12)
Awesome, thanks, everybody. 

Speaker 1  (29:14)
Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (29:15)
No, but. 
